I'm asking you Just slowly letter by
Я вас спрашиваю Просто медленно по
letter Tell me What is the relationship between
буквам Скажите Какое отношение
Nester, who existed in the 10th century in the 10th-1st
Нестер существовавший в X веке в x-1
century, and Ukraine, which
веке имеет отношение к Украине которая
appeared in the 10th century, I must explain Yes, I'm
появилась в X веке обя объясняю Да
not explaining the Old Chronicler Yes, this is one
объясняю не Стар летописец Да это один
of the ancestors of those very people who
из предков Тех самых людей которые
now live on the territory of Ukraine and he is
сейчас живут на территории Украины и он
not the ancestor of the people who live on the
не есть предкам людей которые живут на
territory of Muscovy, the
территории московии
hero city of
город герой
Sevastopol Cool And how is he a
Севастополь Прикольно А чем он
hero, he withstood the defense from
герой герой выдержал оборону с соро
1941 to 1942, therefore he is a
первого по сорок второй год поэтому
hero until 1942, that is, they
герой по сорок второй то есть его
still took him as a result, yes, yes, yes, that
всё-таки взяли в результате да дадада то
means he did not withstand
значит не выдержал
the defense after the third time Yes, he did
оборон после третьего раза Да после
not withstand the third assault Well, that is, he did
третьего штурма не выдержал Ну то есть
not withstand the defense So what is the hero
не выдержал оборон Так а в чём герой
that he withstood the previous two assaults
что предыдущие два штурма
Cool and what are you communicating about I
выдержал Прикольно а чём общаетесь
don't know politics history I saw somewhere
не знаю политика история Я где-то видел
yes a blogger I am a blogger yes yes well politics
да блогер я блогер да да ну политика
history Are you a historian or a
история А вы историк или
politician neither one nor the other I'm just
политик ни то и ни другое просто
wondering what interests you in
интересуюсь что интересует вас по
history what in politics
истории что по политике
ROSI began to be interested in our
РОСИ начали интересоваться нашими
national heroes let's find out what
национальными героями давайте что вас
interests you cold
интересует хол
find out a person
узнать человек
who wanted to cooperate with Russian
который хотел сотрудничать ской
Germany Can he be a national
Германией Может ли являться национальным
hero look And who collaborated with Naka
героем смотри А кто сотрудничал с накой
Germa
Герма
about Bandera sat in a German concentration camp
об Бандера сидел в немецком концлагере
that is, the Germans arrested him on the contrary
то есть немцы его наоборот
The thing is that look not I will
арестовали Дело в том что смотри не я
explain look Bandera lived in Poland on the
объясню смотри Бандера жил в Польше на
territory of Poland Yes when the Soviet
территории Польши Да когда Советский
Union with Germany because the Soviet
Союз с Германией потому что Советский
Union collaborated with Nazi Germany
Союз сотрудничал с нацистской Германией
Yes they attacked Poland together in the
Да они вместе напали на Польшу в три дем
year three and divided Poland Yes having seized the
году и разделили Польшу Да вот захватив
lands on which the wall gang lived the
земли на которых жил стен банда
Soviet for Stepan Bandera was
Советский для Степана Бандеры был
an occupier with Germany attacked his
оккупантов с Германией напал на его
country Yeah so it was not Bandera
страну Угу так это не Бандера
who collaborated with Germany but the Soviet Union
сотрудничал с Германией а Советский Союз
and Stalin collaborated with Germany and
и Сталин сотрудничал с Германией и
attacked the country in which
напали на страну в которой жил
Bandera lived I generally wanted to say not this
Бандера я вообще хотел сказать не это
this but it turns out this look Wait
это а получается это смотри Подожди
look it turns out this let's take
смотри получается это давай возьмём
initially how it was thirty-ninth
изначально же как было тридцать девятый
year Let Bandera lives in Poland Yes he
год Давайте Бандера живёт в Польше Да
drinks coffee there Yes for example coffee there
пьёт кофе себе там Да например каву там
gornyatko coffee drink Yes here in short evil
горнятко кавы пье Да тут короче злой
Hitler  Well, a Nazi with a Nazi if I didn't
Гитлер Ну нацист с нацистом если бы я не
know any of us how could there be,
знаю кто-то из нас как может быть там
for example, some Stalin Yes, who
например какой-то Сталин Да который
collaborated with Hitler Yes, a hero in
сотрудничал с Гитлером Да героем в
Russia Yes, and Stalin and other Soviet
России да и Сталин и другие советские
figures they agreed with Hitler,
эти деятели они вместе с Гитлером
collaborated, shook hands,
договорились сотрудничали пожали руку
signed the pact of ground rent and attacked
подписали пакт молотого рент и напали на
Poland unleashing the First World War WTO
Польшу развязав Первую мировую ВТО
World War Yes, dividing Poland into two
мировую войну Да разделив Польшу на две
parts, the western part was taken by Germany The
части западную забрала Германия
eastern part was
Восточную
taken by the Soviet Union yes
забрала Советский Союз да
yes What do you
да Как вы
think why the Soviet Union was
считаете почему Советский Союз был
an ally of Hitler's Germany in the
союзником гитлеровской Германии в
division of
разделе
Poland in which he
Польши в которой
lived I think
жил считаю
that the Union Treaty Idel
что Союзный договорн Идель
attacked together Yes and Germany took
вместе напали Да и Германия себе забрала
half of Poland for itself and half of Poland was taken by the
пол Польши и пол Польши забрала
Soviet Union in my understanding the Union
Советский Союз в моём понимании Союзный
Treaty was signed between Germany
договор был подписан между Германией
Italy and Japan once again once again Poland was
италией и Японией ещ раз ещ раз Польшу
not taken by Japan for itself not Italy
не Япония забрала себе нени Италия
Poland was taken by Germany and the Soviet
Польшу забрали себе Германия и Советский
Union true yes true that is, the Soviet
Союз правда да правда то есть Советский
Union agreed with Germany to seize
Союз договорился с Германией о захвате
Poland their
Польши их
Soviet Union hit the Slavic brothers
Советский Союз ударил братьям славян
when the Germans attacked  on Poland and the Germans the
когда немцы напали на Польшу и немцы
Poles heroically fought the Germans the
поляки героически сражались с немцами
Soviet Union stabbed the
Советский Союз сделал удар в спину
Slavic brothers the
братьям славянам
Poles in the back it was a thing yes that is the Soviet
полякам было дело да то есть Советский
Union collaborated with Nazi
Союз сотрудничал с гитлеровской
Germany in terms of the occupation of Poland
Германией в плане оккупации Польши
yes I
дахо
admit it is very necessary to be careful Yes
призна очень надо быть осторожным Да
because well on the blade on the hunt the
потому что ну по лезвию на жа охоте
Soviet oh in the Russian Federation Yes
Советском ой в Российской Федерации Да
uh recognition It's just that I am the collaboration of the
ээ признание Просто я коллаборации
Soviet Union with Germany Yes it is
Советского Союза с Германией Да
prosecuted by law If you
преследуется по закону Если вы публично
said publicly and you said it publicly you
сказали а вы сказали это публично вы
were warned What is this Stream that I am a
были предупреждены Что это Стрим что я
blogger Yes you are a blogger you
блогер Да вы блогер у на широкую
confirmed to a wide audience as a citizen of the
аудиторию подтвердили как гражданин
Russian Federation you are now a citizen of the
Российской Федерации вы сейчас гражданин
Russian Federation yes yes Yes you
Российской Федерации да да Да вот вы
confirmed that the Soviet Union
подтвердили что Советский Союз
collaborated with Nazi Germany this is
сотрудничал с гитлеровской Германией это
basically understood in Europe everyone understands in
в принципе в Европе все понимают в
Ukraine everyone understands Russia is
Украине все понимают Россия это
trying to deny this and conducted a criminal
старается отрицать и вела уголовное
offense
преступление
uh for fakes about the Soviet Army and the
ээ за как бы фейки об Советской Армии и
Soviet command That is from
Советском командовании То есть это от
pt to 9 years with confiscation of property
пти до 9 лет с конфискации имущества в
depending on the severity of the crime
зависимости от тяжести преступления у
you have no severity yes That is basically
вас тяжести нет да То есть в принципе
if you  first if this is the first flight
если у вас первая если это первый залёт
yes it was from us Great Britain n No no no
да было со ны Великобритании н Не не нет
no It doesn't matter anymore look at
нет Это уже неважно смотри
the legislation of the Russian Federation Yes it
законодательство Российской Федерации Да
prohibits voicing that the Soviet Union
запрещает озвучивать что Советский Союз
collaborated with Nazi Germany they are
сотрудничал с гитлеровской Германией они
trying to get around it how are you really you are the
стараются это обходить как ты реально ты
first Russian in 2 months who
вот за 2 месяца первый россиянин который
admitted this on live air you are really
признал это в прямом эфире ты реально
great You are brave Not honest I will say You are a
молодец Ты смелый Не честно я скажу Ты
really brave guy I don't know how
реально смелый пацан Я не знаю сколько
old you are little how much
лет мало сколько
Hello You are from hell I
Здравствуйте У ты ёлки-палки вы откуда я
can't hear you Turn on the
вас не слышу Включите
microphone
микрофон Вы
Where are you from Good evening
откуда Добрый вечер
Hello I am from Moscow and where are you from the
Здравствуйте Я из Москвы а вы откуда
city of Khmelnitsky look I am
город Хмельницкий смотрите Я у москвичей
asking Muscovites such an interesting question And
спрашиваю такой интересный вопрос А
how does Moscow relate to
каким образом Москва имеет отношение к
Rus' you are a historian Yes 18 years of practice in
Руси вы историк Да 18 лет практики через
2 years will be the
2 года будет
twentieth Yes education history
двадцатое Да образование стори
education Yes and I
образование Да и археологом
work as an archaeologist awesome
работаю обалденно
candidate you are a candidate of sciences excellent but it is
кандидат вы кандидат наук отлично но мне
hard for me when sciences but I will try to
тяжело када наук но я попытаюсь вс-таки
explain anyway Yes I am asking ordinary people ordinary
объяснить Да я у простого у простых
people I am interested in the opinion of
людей спрашиваю мне интересно мнение
ordinary people Well yes I will try to
простых людей Ну да я попытаюсь вам
explain to you that  firstly the word Rus Yes it
объяснить что во-первых слово Русь Да
is a unifying word it is a unifying
это объединяющее слово это объединяющее
concept which includes
понятие которое в себя
various ethnic groups such as
различные этнические группы такие как
slightly Meria and there Polyane initially Yes for the
чуть меря да там поляне изначально Да
first time the word Rus appeared for
впервые слово Русь появилось
the first time the word Rus appeared in the Ipatiev
впервые слово Русь появилось ипатьевской
Chronicle help
летописи помо
there the word Rus is used Russians
там слово употребляется Русь русские
Russian people Rus is used for the first time
русские люди Русь впервые употребляется
Yes as far as I remember and pack the chronicle
Да насколько я помню и пакую летопись
was written in my opinion in the 10th century You are a historian
написали по-моему в X веке Вы же историк
You should know probably yes It seems to me
Вы должны знать наверно да Мне кажется
you probably want to tell something about
Вы наверно хотите что-то рассказать про
the Tale of Bygone Years and not the Ipatiev
Повесть временных лет а не ипатьев
Chronicle Well it is correctly called the
летопись Ну правильно называется
Ipatiev Chronicle as far as I know it is
ипатьевская летопись насколько я знаю
correctly called the Tale of Times
правильно называется Повесть времен
artistic
художественние
history probably is called the
историе наверное называется всё-таки
Ipatiev Chronicle after all Maybe I am mistaken with the
ипатьевская летопись Может я оши с
Ipatiev Chronicle and the Pois bygone years
ипатьевская летопись и поис ременных лет
are two different documents No these are not
- это два разных документа Нет это не
two different documents this is one two different
два разных документа это один два разных
documents this is one document written the
документа это один документ написанный
Ipatiev Chronicle it is called
ипатьевская летопись она называется
because it was found Yes where there in the
потому что был найден Да где там в доме
Ipatiev house that is why it is called the Ipatiev
ипатьев поэтому называется ипатьевская
Chronicle and it is called the Tale of Bygone
летопись а называется Повесть временных
Years written in 1200 some
лет написанно в 1200 каком-то там
year there  Well, Nestor, the outstanding Nestor,
году Да ну нестором выдающимся нестором
our chronicler Well, not yours, but ours,
нашим летописцем Да ну не вашим а нашим
but yours,
а вашим это
whose
чьим
Ukrainian Ukrainian And how could
украинским украинским А как мог стать
Nestor become your Ukrainian, can you
Нестор вашим украинским вы можете
explain? Because he was here,
объяснить Так потому что он и был тут
how did he become your Moscow One
как он стал вашим московским Секундочку
second, one second, I understand, so the word
секундочку вот я понимаю так что слово
Ukraine appeared in the dem or 18 I understood everything, I
Украина появилось в дем или 18 Всё я
understood, I understood So, look, what is
понял понял понял Значит смотрите в чём
your pro, I explain, I explain, look, the
ваша про а объясняю объясняю смотрите
word Iran appeared in the 20th century Yes, but
слово Иран появилось в XX веке Да но
Iran and Persia are the same thing Yes, they
Иран и Персия - это же есть то же самое
just started to be called, girlfriend,
Да просто началось называться подругу
wait, don't interrupt me Let me as a
подожди не перебивайте меня Дайте я как
historian Now I'll explain to you, look,
историк Теперь вам объясню смотрите ээ
for example, your state was called
ваше государство называлось например
Muscovy Yes, the Moscow Principality, the
Московия Да Московское княжество
Moscow Kingdom was then invented,
Московское царство потом придумали
Russia, the name can change Yes,
Россия название может меняться Да
we can also look at the name,
название также мы можем смотреть
for example,
например
on the territory of Germany Yes, as the
ээ на территории Германии Да как была
Holy Roman Empire was called, it's
священно Римская империя называлась
true, that is, the name You can
правда то есть название Вы можете
come up with any name you like The point is that
придумать какой угодно Суть в том что
Nestor is a chronicler Yes, he was from Kyiv,
Нестор летописец Да он был из киевских а
not
не
Moscow, I'll ask you again
московских ещё раз я вас спрашиваю
Just slowly, letter by letter  Tell me What is the
Просто медленно по буквам Скажите Какое
relation of
отношение
the ner that existed in the century in the century
нер существовавший в веке в ве отношение
to Ukraine that
к Украине кото
appeared I explain Yes I explain not the Old
появись объясняю Да объясняю не Стар
Litopis Yes this is one of the ancestors of those very
литопис Да это один из предков Тех самых
people who now live on the territory of
людей которые сейчас живут на территории
Ukraine and he is not the ancestor of the people
Украины и он не есть предком людей
who live on the territory of
которые живут на территории
Muscovy you understand on the territory of
московии вы понимаете на территории
present-day Ukraine
нынешней Украины
lived the
жили турки
Seljuk Turks the Greeks lived Absolutely right
сельджуки жили греки Абсолютно верно
Absolutely right
Абсолютно верно
Absolutely right then no
Абсолютно верно значит нет
look Greeks Yes they have a relation to the
смотрите греки Да имеют отношение к
history of Ukraine Yes because on the
истории Украины Да потому что на
territory of Ukraine Yes but they are not
территории Украины Да но они не есть
part of the Ukrainian
частью украинского
people ner look I yes Andrey Popk
народа нер смотрите я да Андрей попк
is a direct heir of Nestor
есть прямым наследником Нестора
the chronicler definitely I think the male
летописца однозначно Я думаю мужской
line of the line Yes because my Prat Nestor
линий лини Да потому что Прат мой Нестор
Yes he took the surname Popk because he
Да взял себе фамилию попк потому что он
was a
был
priest and I carry Now he bequeathed the light as
попом и я несу Сейчас свет он как
Nestor Yes according to our family it says
завещал Нестор Да по нашему роду говорит
bring light to these swamps because the
несите свет в эти болота потому что
swamps
болотяна
are calling as far as I remember as far as I know as
зовёт насколько я помню насколько я знаю
far as I my wife is calling I say answer my
насколько я жена зовёт говорю откликнись
wife she will wait come on what does
жене она подождёт давай же что же хочет
Kyiv want after the Invasion  the Tatar-Mongol was
Киев после Нашествия татаро-монгол был
completely cut out and for 200 years it was
вырезан полностью и 200 лет это было
naked this is a lie you made it up The fact is
голая это брехня это вы придумали Дело в
that here is Moscow Yes if we look
том что вот Москва Да если мы смотрим
Moscow was completely burned Yes and under the
Москва была полностью сожжена Да и при
Tatar Mongols and under the French And so
татаро монголах и при французах И так
on and Kyiv once again confirmation
дальше а Киев ещ раз подтверждение того
that Kyiv has
что Киев 200 лет не
not existed for 200 years in Kiev the population of Kyiv did not
лет не существо в ки население Киева не
live in Kiev there was no such thing for 200 years some kind of
валось в Киеве не было 200 лет какого-то
non-settlement you made it up
не заселение это вы придумали только что
just made it up on Why are there records of
просто придумали на Почему есть записи
French historians write again
французских историков писа ещё раз ещё
look again Show me at least
раз посмотри Покажите мне хоть
one real historical
единственный Да реальный исторический
example that in Kyiv for 200 years has not
пример что в Киеве 200 лет не
existed No you claim that therefore you
сущест Нет это вы утверждаете поэтому вы
must show look the Grand
должны показать смотрите Великое
Duchy of Lithuania was there Kyiv was and that
княжество Литовское было туда Киев был и
was all there was Kiev In the Grand Duchy of Lithuania Kyiv
всё не было кие В великом княжестве Киев
was Kyiv under the Grand Duchy of Lithuania
был Киев при великом княжестве Литовской
What are you talking about at all who are you by nickname
Ты что гонишь вообще ты кто по прозванию
at least listen to what I'm saying
вы хотя бы выслушайте что я говорю
wait well you're talking nonsense as if it never happened
подожди ну ты бред несёшь как не было
Kyiv as if Kyiv never existed And where did he get it from
Киева как не было Киева А откуда он взял
when did Kyiv appear again listen
когда взялся Киев снова выслушайте Вы
Can you who founded Kyiv again no Well
можете кто снова основал Киев нет А ну
tell me tell me if Kyiv ceased to
расскажи мне скажи если Киев Прекратил
exist In what year and who
существование В каком году и кто
renewed Kyiv again Great Prince not
возобновил Киев ещё раз Великом княз не
again I turn off your sound once
ещё раз я теб отключаю звук
again I tell you tell me if Kyiv
ещ раз тебе говорю скажи мне если Киева
did not exist after the Tatar
не было после татаро
Angolan
ангольский
Come on
Давай
go again everyone let's go Good evening
идёшь ещё раз всё поехали Добрый вечер
Hello What are you talking about
Здравствуйте О чём общаетесь
Well since you have lag USA something
Ну раз уж у вас лаг США что-то
tells me about the war in Iraq for example I
подсказывает про войну в Ираке к примеру
understood Tell me about the war in Iraq what
понял Расскажите мне о войне в Ираке что
happened there
было
Well the American regime attacked Iraq who fought with whom
Ну режим Америки напал на Ирак кто с кем
Well as I
воевал Ну я так
understand some militants from Iraq and
понимаю какие-то боевики из Ирака и
America And what do you think neither What do you mean
Америка А вы как по вашему ни В смысле
militants I just don't I'm not very strong
боевики я я просто не я не совсем силён
in these matters militants are militants or the
В этих делах боевики то боевики или
state
государство
fought Well what do you think Well it's
воевало Ну как а вы как думаете Ну
just not in my understanding if there is a war yes
просто не в моём понимании если война да
then it is a country fighting with a country if
то это страна со страной воюет если
some militants then they are some kind of
какие-то боевики то это какие-то
terrorists I don't know who with  who fought I
террористы я не знаю кто с кем воевал я
just don't know this story so in
просто не в курсе этой истории так в
Afghanistan there too not with the country
Афганистане там тоже не со страной
wait come on come on about Iraq come on about
подожди давай давай про Ирак давай про
Iraq we'll finish about Iraq we'll help you now about Iraq
Ирак закончим мы сейчас тебя по ираку
Well so with whom who
помо Ну так с кем кто
fought Well it turns out America fought at
воевал Ну получается Америка воевала как
least not with the country But with the militants with the
минимум не со страной А с боевиками с
militants so that was in Iraq
боевиками так то это вона была в Ираке
Wait Stop stop stop that's not a war
Подожди Стоп стоп стоп то это не война
war is when one country fights with
война это когда воюет одна страна с
another country So that was an operation they
другой страной Так это была операция они
called it an operation so don't
это назвали операцией поэтому не ещё раз
look again again war is when two
ещё раз смотри война это когда две
countries fight Yes when some somewhere
страны воюют Да когда какие-то где-то
those are not
те не
necessarily And who what structure
обязательно А кто какая структура
fought against the USA or the USA against what
воевала против США или США против какой
[music]
[музыка]
structure under the structure militants
структуры под структуры боевики
certain Well which what is it
определённые Ну которых как она
called well what is it called this
называется ну как она называется эта
structure
структура
What are militants it's just there
Что такое боевики это просто там
10,000 independent people who
10.000 независимых людей которые себе
just walk around something and shoot each
просто ходят что-то и стреляют каждый
on their own or is it some kind of army
сам по себе или это какая-то армия
maybe well in
может ну вообще по
fact They don't know at all etc. they
факту Они вообще не знаю проче они
fought they just bombed the civilian
воевали они бомбили просто мирное
population just like that wait wait So
население просто так подожди подожди Так
they  with militants or with
они с боевиками воевали или с мирным
civilians I can't understand bomb well those who
населением бом не могу понять ну те кто
stood up can be called militants Name me
вставал можно назвать боевика Назови мне
three cities of Iraq
три города Ирака
So you said You are not strong in this
Так вы же сказали Вы не сильны в этой
topic Where did you name them from I'm interested yes
теме Откуда назви мне интересно да
I just want Three cities and you said you
просто я хочу Три города и вы сказали вы
don't know I'll check now Come on three
не знаете я сейчас проверю Давай три
cities Iraq not it just seemed to me
города Ирак не мне просто показалось вы
you started checking me somehow yeah yeah yeah
вы начали меня как-то проверять дада
yeah three cities of Iraq or two rivers
дадада три города Ирака или две речки
that flow through Iraq don't Google
которые через Ирак протекают не Гугли
take your hands away raise up ru I only know
руки забери подними ру Я знаю только
Baghdad Iraq and that's it Well Baghdad is the
Багдад Ирак и всё Ну Багдад - это
capital Yes as well as two other cities of Iraq and
столица Да как и ещё два города Ирака и
I know that American Nazis bombed
я знаю что американские нацисты бомбили
Baghdad
багда
[music]
[музыка]
Why can't Russia be bombed as well Tell
Почему России нельзя бомбить также Скажи
me Tell me name two rivers that
мне Скажи назви мне две речки которые
flow Iraq two rivers
текут Ирак две речки
some at least one well
какие-то одну хотя
look first of all Do you definitely know
бы ну смотрите вопервых Ты точно знаешь
these two rivers if you are an expert on Iraq
две эти реки если ты специалист по ираку
You know I just by No well by warriors those
Ты знаешь я просто по Не ну по воинам те
two rivers that flow in Iraq
две речки которые протекают в Ираке
are known like this a Prim here war sheet by
известны так а Прим тут война лист по
river now now now well we  by
речка сейчас сейчас сейчас ну мы по
cities those There in the rivers they drowned these
городам те Там же в речках топили эти
USA drowned in short in the rivers
США топила короче в речках повстанцев
these rebels we should know and the cities except
этих то мы должны знаем а города кроме
Baghdad Baghdad We know I only know
багда багдада Знаем мы я только знаю
the situation with Baghdad when they bombed well
ситуация с багдадом когда бомбили хорошо
and now the second question why after the
а теперь второй вопрос почему после
American invasion Yes the Americans
американского вторжения Да американцы
forced the state to change its name from
заставили переименоваться государство с
Iraq to
Ирака в
Iran Hmm it seems to me you do not understand
Иран Хм мне кажется вы не разбираетесь в
this topic because firstly you
этой теме потому что во-первых Вы
confirmed that you do not understand
подтвердили что вы не разбираетесь в
this topic because Iran is
этой теме потому что Иран - это
firstly well Iran is Iran I was
во-первых ну Иран - это Иран Это я тебя
testing you Well no need to make excuses
проверял Ну не надо оправдываться
firstly you do not understand the topic I see
во-первых вы не разбираетесь в теме я ви
what are you trying to build yourself as an American but
что пытаетесь себя строить американце но
you live in Ukraine I live in Ukraine but
живёте вы в Украине Я живу в Украине да
don't ask me I'm not
ты же меня не спрашивай я же тебе не
telling you that I'm an American I live in Ukraine
говорю что я американец Я живу в Украине
yes So tell me if if I lived in
да Так расскажи мне если если б я жил в
America I would know about the soldiers of America Yes
Америке я бы знал про воины Америки Да
tell me a Ukrainian who fought in
расскажи мне украинцу кто м воевал в
Iraq What cities
Ираке Какие города
were bombed Well I already told everyone what you will
бомбили Ну я я уже всём сказал что вы на
say to this not you said only  there is
это скажете не вы сказали только багда
no such thing as where they bombed Show me
этого нет то что бомбили где Покажи мне
where they bombed
где бомбили
Baghdad there somewhere in what year
Багдад там вот там где-то в каком году
it
это вообще
was Well, look, let's say you're
было Ну вы смотрите вот допустим вы меня
trying to understand me now I want to understand Don't look I
сейчас пытаетесь хочу понять Не смотри я
want to understand Well, tell me what they bombed in
хочу понять ну ты говори что бомбили в
what year they bombed
каком году бомбили
America Bombed Baghdad In what year And
Америка Бомбила Багдад В каком году А
if I don't know the year, that is, this didn't
если я не знаю года это что этого не
happen Well, at least approximately so that I
было Ну приблизительно хотя бы чтобы я
understand Maybe you made it up You did it You're
понимал Может вы придумали Вы же так Вы
not an expert Well, okay, I'll check Well
же не Эксперт Ну хорошо я я проверю Ну
then why did I make it up So, that is, you
тогда зачем я придумал Так то есть ты
admitted that you're a
признал что ты
chatterbox Well, America, they didn't bomb
Балабол Ну Америка они не бомбили ни
Libya or Iraq Look again, you
Ливию ни Ирак смотри ещё раз ты признал
just admitted that you had
только что что ты до этого
deceived before Well, someone can say that
обманул ну вы кто-то может сказать что
it's like it wasn't you You first said one thing
так типа не ты Ты сначала сказал одно
no stop stop not Ukrainian You first
нет стоп стоп не украинский Ты сначала
said one thing and then you said Yes I
говорил одно а потом ты сказал Да я
told a lie That is, you deceived you
сказал неправду То есть ты обманул ты
said First one thing then you admitted you
сказал Сначала одно потом ты признал ты
admitted not Ukrainian historians And you
признал не украинский историки А ты
admitted that there was no such thing
признал сда такого не
Well, then why do you think that I will
было Ну так а почему вы думаете что я
move in your direction It turns out Well,
буду по-вашему двигаться получается Ну
that's you You first said one thing and then you
так ты Ты сначала сказал одно а потом
said no Yes that's not true  well dare
сказал нет Да это не так не ну на слабо
stop what dare I didn't take dare I
стоп при чём слабо я на слабо не брал я
just wanted to understand and during the
просто хотел понять и ты в процессе
conversation you retracted your words now
разговора отказался от своих слов теперь
I didn't retract then you say that you didn't
то я не отказался то ты говоришь что не
attack those are not no stop you said that
нападал те не нет стоп ты сказал что
now you didn't attack you said it I have
тепер не нападал ты это сказал у меня
it all recorded You said That is you
это всё записано Ты сказал То есть ты
got it recorded in your head everything
получил записывается в голове все
that you watch you
которые вы смотрит вы
all come on lira
все давай лира
Relax this is a recording I'll
Расслабься это запись я это
cut it out no need like Let people know
вырежу ну не надо типа Пусть люди знают
the truth Armed Forces and about Iraq cut it out
правду ВС и про Ирак вырежите
And I'll leave it just so you can
И я оставлю как раз чтобы ты
embarrass Well
позо Ну
okay well then tell me what happened in America
ладно ну так расскажи что было в Америке
what happened in
что было в
America in America
Америке в Америке
itself there America that the SES
там самой амери что сес
is going on with Iran let's
проходит с ирам дава
finish it off in Iraq so Let's answer my
добьём по ираку так А давайте вы на мои
questions
вопросы
like this You said what happened in
ответите так Ты же сказал что было в
Iraq Explain to me what happened who fought with whom
Ираке Объясни мне что было кто с кем
I've already said everything No and why are you
воевал я уже всё сказал Нет а что ты
nervous why are you swearing
нервничаешь что ты матюкается
[laughter]
[смех]
Poor thing so fried pressed Well
Бедняжка так аш поджаренный поджали Ну
tell me Explain to me
расскажи Объясни мне
Man and underburnt podra Tell me so
Челове а подгора подра Расскажи мне да
what happened  in Iraq Come on you opened your mouth
что ж было в Ираке Давай ты открыл рот
about Iraq Tell me Yes even if you
за Ирак Расскажи мне Да даже если бы эту
knew this topic 100% You had a victory
тему на все 100% знал У вас же перемога
there anyway Tell Tell me Yes what
там всё равно бы Раскажи Расскажи Да что
happened what happened Vira Tell me you not you
ж было что было Вира Раскажи ты не вы ты
you would have turned everything inside out this would not have happened that
ты бы всё вывернул этого бы не было что
they are not Nazis
они не нацисты
What Come on Tell me what happened in
Что давай Давай расскажи что было в
Iraq what happened in Iraq
Ираке что было в Ираке
come on every liberal who lives
давай так каждый либерал который живёт
There in Germany in Europe now they
Там в Германии в Европе вот сейчас это
hear it like this
слышат такие
you you understand Russia It is
просто вас вас понимаете Россия Она
only getting stronger I live in
только сильнее становится Я живу в
Russia ute ute there in the chat you have a
России уте уте там в чате у тебя
salary I have a salary millions
зарплата у меня зарплата миллионы
millions you are all in Europe you All I am Russia
миллионы вы все в Европе вы Всё я Россия
How much is your
Сколько у тебя
[laughter]
[смех]
salary at
зарплата при
So come on about Iraq So tell me what
Так давай по ираку Так расскажи что же
happened in Iraq Come on Che are you latching onto
было в Ираке Давай Че прицепились к
this Ira it was you who said you started Iraq
этому Ира это вы сказали вы начали Ирак
you took asked about Iraq you started the
вы взяли спросили про Ирак вы начали
topic Let's finish the topic about Iraq I want
тему Давайте добьём тему по ираку Я хочу
about Ukraine about America you said not you
про Украину про Америку вы сказали не вы
said about Iraq like well what was bombed there
сказали про Ирак типа ну что там бомбили
let's in what years you will not check
давайте в каких это годах вы не проверте
What is the point of me to you  I can't tell you I
Какой смысл мне вам рассказывать я не
understand Well who
могу Поня Ну кто на кого
attacked whom America
напал Америка в сле
followed the troops in Afghanistan So
ко шты вели войска в Афганистане Так
stop stop stop stop stop stop stop what
стоп стоп стоп стоп стоп стоп а что
is it Let's start with Kuwait What
такое Давайте начнём ещё с Кувейта Что
is
такое
Kuwait Well the country
Кувейт Ну страна
so Iraq attacked
так Ирак напал на
Kuwait Operation Desert Storm then
Кувейт операция Буря в пустыне потом
after that it was
после это было
like this Desert Storm is actually
такое Буре пустыни - это вообще-то
America if anything yes yes yes a
Америка если что
consequence of Iraq's attack on
дадада следствием нападения Ирака на
Kuwait that is Iraq attacked Kuwait As a
Кувейт то есть Ирак напал на Кувейт В
result of which there would have been in the desert When
следствие чего было бы в пусты Коть
the war the Americans built blood Shed the
война американцы строили крово Пролит
war once again no no stop stop stop
войну по ещё раз нет нет стоп стоп стоп
let's do it like that the Americans attacked
давай так э американцы нападали на на
Iraq before Iraq's attack on
Ирак до нападения Ирака на
Kuwait No well I don't know it could be
Кувейт Нет ну я не знаю это может быть
somehow Propaganda What So stop stop
както Пропаганда Какая Так стоп стоп
stop stop stop stop stop Let's look at the
стоп стоп стоп стоп Давай посмотрим по
dates Yes when Iraq attacked Kuwait and
датам Да когда Ирак напал на Кувейт и
when the US is the matter of who is attacking whom
когда э США дело кто на кого нападает
they figure it out themselves Because
они сами разбираются Потому что потому
because no Kuwait is an allied country of the US Well
что нет Кувейт - это союзники США были А
then Donbass is an allied country of Russia that's
ну так Донбасс - это союзники России вот
why no no no no no
к че нет нет нет нет нет
you are now you are sitting in  puddle sat in a puddle
м ты сейчас ты сел в лужу сел в лужу
because Kuwait was a universally recognized
потому что Кувейт было признанное всем
international state Yes, a member of the UN Yes,
международное государство Да член ООН Да
neither the DPR nor the LPR were universally recognized parts of
ни ДНР и лнр признанная всеми часть
Ukraine, that is, you just
Украины была то есть ты как раз сейчас
sat in a puddle now you sat in a puddle you disgraced
сел в лужу ты сел в лужу ты опозорил
yourself with Iraq Now you disgraced yourself with
себя с ираком Теперь ты опозорил себя с
Donetsk Lugansk in Donetsk Lugansk the
Донецком Луганском в Донецке луган
Russian Intervention took place in
произошла Российская Интервенция в 14м
2014, occupation as with Crimea, yes As
году оккупация как и с Крымом да В
a result of which they then proclaimed
результате чего там провозгласили потом
some kind of puppet governments that's
марионеточный какие-то правительства вот
all You screwed up
и всё Ты облажался
Sid you screwed up for the second time look Yes, you
Сид ты облажался второй раз смотри Да ты
really are just like this yes, you can't do
реально просто вот такой да ты не можешь
anything you run you poor thing you think how can
ничего ты бегаешь ты бедняжка думаешь
you switch Yes, you specifically
как вы переключиться Да ты специально
say nasty things there so that I would
там гадости говори чтобы я вроде тебя
switch you off yes, you sent No, we
переключил да те послал Нет мы тебя
are frying you, this is it, but he disappeared disappeared yes
прожариваем это а слился слился да да
yes That's it, come on, go That's it And how
Всё давай идёшь Вот так А какой он
impudent he was, he wanted to come out
дерзкий был вышел
Oh, how I love such fries
хотел Ах как я люблю так такие прожарок
I love to subscribe to my Instagram I don't
Я люблю пидпишить на мий Instagram Я не
know  why is this for you why is this still there
знаю для чего це тоб для чего ще тоб там
to watch on the axis and face But for you it's
дивитись на ось й фейс Але для тебе це
one two or three clicks But you try
один два або три клика Але ты тримае
me and I will click Wow in me there are a lot of
мене и я буду кти Вау в мене там Купа
fouls and in me there will be a cool mood to
фолов и в мене буде класний настр щоб
do but cool video letter on my
робити но крут вдео пись на мий
Instagram until Andriy like
Instagram пок Андрий вот
this come on I'm waiting for you and
так давай я тебя